So our job has got finished Monday.
It took actually almost an hour, you see,
and if you go to the S3 data lake, we see the data
for even year 2095 and for the different months.
And within the months, we have data
for different days as well.
So we gotta be tuning this, okay?
The question is whether 59 minutes
is acceptable to us or not.
We'll discuss about that later.
The tuning part, we'll talk about that later.
But we'll now proceed to creating the next job,
which loads the data into the aggregated layer
by reading from curated layer. But
Before we go to the next part, can you think about why
this job ran longer When we ran a script, when we ran it
as a notebook, it hardly took a few minutes.
Think about that. And
before you look at what others have said below, I want you
to think about that and comment in the comment section about
why you think about why you think the script ran longer.